Name Thor Wessel Lindberg

Address Reykjavík, Iceland
Email thor@lindberg.is

Website lindberg.is

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/thorlindberg

Profile/interests I bring a cross-disciplinary background in medical science, information technology and user-

centred design. With my experience as a Consultant, I bring an understanding of client- and investor-oriented work and project planning. In my spare time I enjoy building software, learning about technologies, and traveling throughout the U.S. to network with others in the tech sector.

Experience

08/2022 — 12/2023 **Netcompany**

IT Consultant

· Analyzed and documented existing business processes on 2 projects for 2 clients.

· Contributed to new Java source code on 1 project for 1 client.

10/2021 - 07/2022 National Special Crime Unit

IT-Administrative Student

Managed users of webportal and provided direct support.

08/2021 - 06/2022 IT University of Copenhagen

Teaching Assistant

· Assisted with courses in Python, JavaScript, MQTT, and UX design.

Shift Leader

Education

08/2020 — 06/2022 Master of Science in Digital Design IT University of Copenhagen

08/2017 — 07/2020 Bachelor of Science in Health Informatics Copenhagen University

Skills

Development React, React Native, JavaScript, TypeScript, Swift, SwiftUI, UIKit, Java, MATLAB, Azure, Git

Data analysis Python, NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib

Design Figma, components, variants, interactive flows, auto layout

Language Fluent in English. Beginner at Icelandic

Published

App Store **Áfangastaður - Explore Iceland** apps.apple.com/app/id6466740299

Package react-native-modal-provider npmjs.com/react-native-modal-provider